http://www.queenmary.org.uk/privacy/

Show more
Like most websites we uses cookies. In order to deliver a personalised, responsive service and to improve the site, we remember and store information about how you use it. This is done using simple text files called cookies which sit on your computer. These cookies are completely safe and secure and will never contain any sensitive information. They are used only by us. The information you provide will be used solely for dealing with you for your activities at Queen Mary Sailing Club. The club has a data privacy policy which can be found at https://queenmary.bookinglive.com/the-club/club-documents your data will be stored and used in accordance with this policy'.
Accept
Club
COVID-19 Members Guidance and BookingAdult Courses 2021Junior Courses 2021Day SailPersonal TuitionFacilitiesOpening TimesClub DocumentsLocationClub TripsDiscounts for MembersAnnual General Meeting 2020Council Members Accommodation RYA PublicationsRecruitmentHistory
JOIN US
Standard MembershipAdult Select (Monthly Subscription)Youth Select (Monthly Subscription)Boat and Board HireOpen Day
LEARN TO
Sailing
Club FleetsSailabilitySaturday ClubBart’s BashTaster SessionsBoats for SaleMembers CoachingQM Sail Foiling
RS21
Discover KeelboatingKeelboat CoursesRS21 Introduction to RacingRS21 Inland ChampionshipsRS21 Keelboat Club
Racing
Restart Racing 2020Club RacingOpen MeetingsResultsBloody MarySailing CommitteeRace OfficersTracTracTrophies
Windsurfing
Speed ChallengeTraining ClinicsWindsurf Kit for SaleBoard HireStand Up Paddleboarding SUPSuper Mile ChallengeSimon Winkley Windsurf CoachingAdult W-surf Courses
Courses
Easter, Summer and Half Term 3 Day Courses YouthAdultWinter Training (Adult Programme) PowerboatInstructorOnline and Shore Based CoursesBespokeJunior Course Briefing Vouchers
Youth
Summer Race Training (Youth)Youth GroupWinter TrainingLondon Youth GamesWindsurfing Team 15NSSAQM Youth Open Meeting
Activities
School Activity daysCorporate Team BuildingMeeting FacilitiesChildren’s Birthday PartiesDof EPlastic EducationLap the Lake
NEWS
Contact
Privacy
Home > Privacy
Queen Mary Sailing Club Data Privacy Policy
Why do we collect and process personal information?
To administer membership records and collect fees
To publicise events and activities at the Club
To maintain duty registers and notify members of their duties
To publish race results
To provide information to those attending courses or events
To comply with our bye-laws, for example notifying members of the AGM
For gathering aggregated data for RYA and other reporting.
The categories of information that we collect and store include:
Contact information for members, temporary members and those making venue bookings (eg name, address, email address, telephone number)
Medical and dietary information for those attending training courses
Attendance information for analysis and aggregated reporting
Characteristics (in particular disability) for RYA reporting purposes
Photos and videos of members and visitors taking part in Club events
CCTV recordings for security
Who do we share this information with?
Officers of the club receive appropriate information to enable them to fulfil their duties such as organising and running training courses, administering duties, administering membership renewal
Aggregated attendance and disability data is shared with the RYA but this does not include personal information
Name and any contact details provided are made available to other Race Officers on Dutyman (the Race Officer duty management system)
CCTV recordings are shared with the police at their request.
Videos and photos of members and visitors taking part in club events are posted on our website and other social media channels
We will not share your personal information with any third parties apart from those stated here without your prior advance permission.
Changing or updating your personal information
If you wish to come off any of our distribution lists, use the unsubscribe option or email the sender.
For all other requests, send an email to sailondon@queenmary.org.uk
Requesting access to your personal data
You have the right to request access to information that we hold about you. To make such a request, send an email to sailondon@queenmary.org.uk
Questions or Comments on this Policy
If you would like to discuss anything concerning this policy, send an email to sailondon@queenmary.org.uk
Last Updated May 2018
